const interactiveSystemDesign_questions = [
  {
    question: "What involves designing interactive systems with the needs, preferences, and capabilities of users at the forefront?",
    answer: "User-Centered Design",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What is a critical aspect of interactive system design, focusing on the ease of learning, efficiency of use, and user satisfaction?",
    answer: "Usability",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the point of interaction between the user and the system, involving visually appealing layouts and intuitive navigation structures?",
    answer: "User Interface Design",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What involves organizing and structuring information within the system to make it easy for users to find and understand?",
    answer: "Information Architecture",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What focuses on defining how users interact with the system and how the system responds to user input?",
    answer: "Interaction Design",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What ensures interactive systems are accessible to users of all abilities, including those with disabilities?",
    answer: "Accessibility",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What ensures interactive systems adapt to different screen sizes and resolutions, providing a consistent user experience across devices?",
    answer: "Responsive Design",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What is an iterative process of prototyping, testing, and refining design solutions based on user feedback?",
    answer: "Iterative Design Process",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What involves gathering feedback from users and analyzing usage data to improve interactive systems?",
    answer: "User Feedback and Analytics",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  },
  {
    question: "What often requires collaboration between designers, developers, and stakeholders from various disciplines?",
    answer: "Cross-Disciplinary Collaboration",
    category: "interactiveSystemDesign"
  }
];

export default interactiveSystemDesign_questions;
